#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/myun (LinkedIn) myun.live (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Office Leadership Public Speaking

### Languages

Korean (Native or Bilingual) English (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

Introduction to Clinical Data Science Fundamentals of Quantitative Modeling

Design and Interpretation of Clinical Trials

### Honors-Awards

Dean's Honor List

# Mike Yun

Data Scientist | Part-time Grad Student Cypress, California

# Summary

A proven talent for aligning business strategy and objectives with established data analytics and logistics operations management paradigms to achieve maximum operational impacts with minimum resource expenditures. A growth-focused thought leader with expertise spanning data and analysis, military operations, relationship management, technology solutions, management development, operations optimization, and project management. Exceptionally dedicated professional with keen interpersonal, communication, and organizational skills, as well as personnel management, policy development, and resource allocation expertise.

# Experience

Anti-Fragility Health
Data Scientist
January 2020 - Present (3 months)
United States

U.S. Army and Army National Guard Logistics Manager July 2017 - Present (2 years 9 months) Bell, California

- Served as executive officer, operations supervisor, and supply chain manager for an integrated organization consisting of 320 personnel and over 100 vehicles / rolling stock, weaponry, and communication devices
- Spearheaded a \$10 million in assets through data management and department projections
- Over three years of experience in data, logistics, and warehouse management
- Conducted inventories and internal and external audits of over \$4 million in assets and 300 soldiers
- Built complex GCSS reports to audit \$4 million of assets, bench stock, and man-hours for over 300 individual records

- Developed a brand new metrics report that gave the brigade its very first internal system to effectively analyze product and vendor data
- Audited inventory transactions according to corporate standards and conducted investigative analysis to provide the appropriate resolutions
- Direct monthly cross-functional team meetings as part of the forecast, inventory, and distribution operations continuous improvement process
- Acted as the liaison between front-line units and sustainment brigades to provide effective logistical support
- Organized and reported training statistics to company-wide management

Advanced Research Center, Inc. Data Analyst January 2017 - July 2017 (7 months) Anaheim, California

- Supported statistics and data management, clinical programming, clinical operations, clinical pharmacology, medical writing and regulatory groups as a clinical systems administrator
- Reviewed and analyzed EMR, SAS Datasets, Clinical Database, and Clinical Research Forms to ensure an accurate and clean database
- Reviewed protocols, designed case report forms, reviewed case report forms, and documented data problems
- Built databases to capture data for quality improvement and clinical effectiveness projects
- Supported and assisted other Clinical Data Associates and Managers working on trials. Provided status reports, as requested, on the progress of the trial
- Report and Query Writer using Excel, Relational Database, using SQL with software application (TOAD) Tool for Oracle Application Developers
- Communicate with internal associates and external clients such as Doctors,
   Clinical Research Investigators, Managers, Clinical Data Analyst, and Study
   Coordinators
- Performed manual and programmatic validation review of all incoming data and case report forms
- Interfaced between the sites and the sponsor, escalated issues when necessary
- Maintained contact lists for study locations and conducted outreach to sites when needed
- Redesigned and implemented clinical departments' backup infrastructure including the implementation of Offsite Storage of critical clinical trial data

UC Davis Center for Mind and Brain Laboratory Research Assistant November 2015 - April 2016 (6 months)

Davis, CA

- Participated in two research studies in psychology and cognitive neuroscience determining the correlation between music and neural and statistical results
- Participated in a research study observing electroencephalography (EEG)-based auditory emotion
- Participated in a longitudinal research study collecting survey data on autobiographical memory triggered by music in a controlled environment
- Studied whether the auditory system exhibited a similar organization for various emotion categories and how acoustic features influence non-verbal sound emotional perception
- Pre-screened participants using self-report data via surveys
- Analyzed and organized experimental data on Microsoft Excel
- Reworked lab reports and manifests; revised for grammar, content, and logical coherency
- Administered and supervised the use of EEG on participants in an experimental setting
- Distributed various research questionnaires for participants and managed the data collection and distribution
- Researched psychological studies regarding the relationship between audio and emotions/memory

#### Elance

Translator

June 2015 - December 2015 (7 months)

Cypress, CA

- Translated financial documents from Korean to English and vice versa
- Translated for military-related games
- Completed all assignments within 2-3 business days of requested initiation date with quality
- Consulted with clients to organizing documents to adhere to the translated language
- · Created self-advertisements to promote my translating service

U.S. Army and Army National Guard

**Combat Engineer** 

November 2011 - November 2015 (4 years 1 month)

#### Santa Rosa, CA

- Trained, maintained, and influenced a team of five personnel on basic combat and clearance operations one-weekend per month
- Created and maintained a positive working interpersonal climate in a highstress environment
- Responsible for cataloging and maintaining \$ 10,000 worth of equipment with 0% loss
- Coordinated the exchange of materials and information regarding combat classes
- Performed basic combat construction of fighting positions and wire entanglements
- Operated various light or heavy engineer wheeled vehicles
- Prepared and installed priming and firing systems for demolition and explosives
- Supervise lower grade soldiers and provide technical guidance to soldiers in their duties

UC Davis Center for Neuroscience Research Assistant June 2015 - September 2015 (4 months) Davis, CA

- Participated in behavioral studies to study human spatial memory
- Acquired and recorded data using Excel via both qualitative and quantitative assessments
- Collected and streamlined participant data
- Used Unity to design visual aspects of the study; used Oculus Development kit to explore research options
- Regularly conducted data cleanup to enhance the overall quality of the data

University of California, Davis Peer Advisor August 2014 - June 2015 (11 months) Davis, CA

- Provided academic advising to undergraduate students majoring and minoring in Music
- Provided information regarding policies, procedures, and referrals to resources related to the Music
- Department, College of Letters and Science, and UC Davis
- Provided administrative support to the supervising staff advisers

- Represented the Arts Group Advising Center and the Music Department at outreach events
- Upheld diversity and an awareness of multicultural issues in higher education
- Taught and assisted with music theory concepts and assignments to students majoring in music

**Davis Joint Unified School District** Teaching Intern March 2014 - June 2014 (4 months)

Davis, CA

- Taught violin, viola, and cello to elementary school students at Marguerite Montgomery Elementary
- Conducted string section rehearsals
- Created individualized lesson plans for students based on student level
- Taught basic music theory

The California Aggie Writer

January 2013 - March 2013 (3 months)

Davis, CA

- Informed UC Davis students of the current events through newspaper articles
- Went to music venues and critiqued on Arts section

## Education

**Boston University** 

Master of Science - MS, Data Analytics · (2020 - 2021)

University of California, Davis

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Music and Psychology · (2011 - 2016)